Charles Wharton Stork Papers
Charles Wharton Stork Papers
- Writings (1993 accession)
  - Misc. poems (Box 11)
  - Winter Scene from a Bridge, typescript poem and holograph (Box 11)
  - Trails, typescript poem (Box 11)
  - Lekha, typescript story (Box 11)
  - Contents and Section Division of Have Faith, typescript book of poetry (Box 12)
  - Article in Old Penn Weekly Review of CWS German translation, typescript – novel (Box 12)
  - Flower Inferno, translation by CWS (Box 12)
  - Pnncess Flora, holograph novel manuscript (Box 12)
  - Living Greece, typescript story (Box 12)
  - Mis-Statement, typescript poem and holograph (Box 12)
  - The Stupid Swede (Box 12)
  - Danish Poetry, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Discarded Christmas Tree, typescript poem (Box 12)
  - This Morning, Getting Out of Bed, typescript poem (Box 12)
  - The Death of Orpheus, typescript poem (Box 12)
  - Ulysses of the Sirens, typescript poem (Box 12)
  - A Vision of Misjudgment, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - What's Wrong With Poetry Now?, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - A Hell of a Critic, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Personal Memories of Owen Wister, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Sons and Daughters of the Vikings, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Great and Near Great, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Eduard Mörke, German Lyric Poet, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Equipment of a Critic, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - S. Lanier, A Poet we are Catching Up to, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Unattained Meredith, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Flacon by Per Hallstrom, translation by CWS printed essay (Box 12)
  - Bernard Shaw, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - DuBose Heyward, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Ariel and Endymion, typescript and holograph essay (Box 12)
  - Adventures While Discovering a Novel, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Portion of a play, typescript (Box 12)
  - An essay on Food and Eating, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Three Variations, typescript story (Box 12)
  - To Edwin Arlington Robinson, typescript poem (Box 12)
  - Misc. poems (Box 12)
  - Poetry (Box 12)
  - Poetry (Box 12)
  - The Voice, A Key to Character, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Ballad in English Literature, typescript book (Box 12)
  - Three Unpublished Anecdotes From the Life of Barrie, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Whittier Rediscovered, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Erik Axel Karlfeldt, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Sketch History of the English Popular Ballad (Box 12)
  - Landor's Conversations, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - A Visit to Pandit Nehru, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Master to Novice, typescript story (Box 12)
  - A Changeling Transformed, typescript story (Box 12)
  - Unidentified play fragment, typescript (Box 12)
  - Early Recollections of Ezra Pound, holograph essay (Box 12)
  - The White Top Festival, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Twice Facing Death, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Exhilarating Craft of Letters, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Hemingway and the Exotics, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Walt Whitman Today, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Dancer in a Cage, typescript story (Box 12)
  - Fording the Continent, typescript story (Box 12)
  - Siena, typescript story (Box 12)
  - Manuscript, A guest of the Navy, holograph story (Box 12)
  - Misc. writings (Box 12)
  - Published essays (Box 12)
  - Misc. writings (Box 12)
  - On Being an Oriental, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - Violence on Trial, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - The Home Breaker, typescript story (Box 12)
  - Luncheon with W.B. Yeats in his Attic, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - A Henchman of G. Vasa, typescript novel (Box 12)
  - How Old was Miranda, typescript essay (Box 12)
  - West Meets East, typescript poems and holograph (Box 12)
  - Unidentified Story fragment, typescript (Box 12)
  - Misc. music (Box 12)
  - Misc. poems in envelope, typescript (Box 12)
  - Misc. poems in envelope, holograph (Box 12)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 12)
  - Misc. writings and fragments (Box 12)
  - The Home Breaker, typescript story in envelope (Box 13)
  - The Home Breaker, typescript and holograph story in envelope (Box 13)
  - Northland Magic, typescript story in envelope (Box 13)
  - Mason and Dixon's Line, typescript story (Box 13)
  - Misc. poems (Box 13)
  - Back in High, typescript novel manuscript in envelope (Box 13)
  - Misc. stories (Box 13)
  - Swanhild, typescript play (Box 13)
  - Summary of play 'Susie's Grandmother', typescript (Box 13)
  - A Daughter of Boston, holograph play in notebook (Box 13)
  - Four Kisses, typescript novel in binder (Box 13)
  - Ballads, typescript poems (Box 13)
  - Sonnets, typescript poems (Box 13)
  - Have Faith in America and Other Verses, typescript poems in binder (Box 13)
  - Back in High, typescript novel in envelope (Box 13)
  - Shy Adventurer, typescript novel in envelope (Box 13)
  - Swanhild, typescript play in envelope (Box 13)
  - Renee, typescript play in envelope (Box 13)
  - Aunt Elsbettel, typescript play in envelope (Box 13)
  - Falstaff on Broadway (Box 13)
  - The Death of Orpheus, typescript poem (Box 13)
  - A Quaker Mother, typescript play (Box 13)
  - Erika, typescript opera in envelope (Box 13)
  - Misc. writings and fragments, typescript (Box 13)
  - In Earthen Vessels, typescript novel wrapped in cardboard (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems (Box 14)
  - A Henchman of Gustaf Vasa, typescript novel wrapped in cardboard (Box 14)
  - 'Elsa the Precocious' and 'Den Kloka Elsa', typescript novel and book in box (Box 14)
  - Animals Nobody Knows, typescript children's poems and illustrations in binder (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems inspired by Martha's Vineyard and the New England beach, typescript (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems (Box 14)
  - A Frenchman Pays His Debts, typescript story (Box 14)
  - Needed, typescript story (Box 14)
  - The End of Every Maid's Desire, typescript story (Box 14)
  - The Nails, holograph poem (Box 14)
  - Modern Swedish Poetry, typescript essay (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Under the Lion's Paw, typescript story (Box 14)
  - Sea Song (words by CWS), music (Box 14)
  - Alcibiades (?), typescript play (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 14)
  - Untitled poem, holograph (Box 14)
  - A week in the Poconos, typescript essay (Box 14)
  - American Bards Through British Eyes (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Honor to Abbie Huston Evans, typescript essay (Box 14)
  - An Heir of Prophesy, typescript story (Box 14)
  - Marta of Sillen, typescript essay (Box 14)
  - A Russian Treasure Room, typescript essay (Box 14)
  - A Nile Panorama, typescript and holograph essay (Box 14)
  - Adventures in the Danish Lyric, typescript and holograph essay (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Misc. essays (Box 14)
  - American Magazine Poetry, holograph essay (Box 14)
  - Reviews by CWS (Box 14)
  - Reviews of CWS translations (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Translated poems, typescript and holograph (Box 14)
  - Flower Inferno by Ernst Löhndorff, translated by CWS holograph (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems (Box 14)
  - Misc. writings (Box 14)
  - Misc. poems (Box 14)
  - DuBose Heyward: Personal Recollections, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Three Variations, typescript story (Box 15)
  - With a Mouth Organ, typescript story (Box 15)
  - A Wicket Intrigue, typescript story (Box 15)
  - A. Edward Newton, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - 'The Poetic Year' extract, by William Stanley Braithwaite, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 15)
  - The Quarter Deck, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - The Birth of Laughter, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - The Quarter Deck, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - A. Edward Newton, holograph essay (Box 15)
  - Luncheon with W.B. Yeats in his Attic, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Edna St. Vincent Millay, as Poet and as Person, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - Luncheon with W.B. Yeats in his Attic, holograph essay (Box 15)
  - Uncle Ananias, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - The Hosiery Show, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Ezra Pound to Himself, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Finding Alice, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - A Mirage, typescript story (Box 15)
  - The Something Else, typescript story (Box 15)
  - The Baffled Grouch, typescript story (Box 15)
  - With Sabres, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Companions of the Bath, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Clayton's Kick, typescript story (Box 15)
  - The Wonder Bird, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Duets, typescript and holograph poem (Box 15)
  - Course materials (Box 15)
  - The Russian Mutineers, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Misc. writings, holograph (Box 15)
  - Edwin Arlington Robinson, typescript and holograph essay (Box 15)
  - Misc. notes, holograph (Box 15)
  - Reviews by CWS (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - Unidentified play fragment, typescript and holograph (Box 15)
  - Misc. writings and fragments, holograph (Box 15)
  - Streamlined Grandma, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Ferment in the Far East by Mark A. Nourse, reviewed by CWS (Box 15)
  - And Gazelles Leaping by Sadhin N. Ghose, reviewed by CWS (Box 15)
  - Misc. reviews by CWS (Box 15)
  - Pastoral, musical score, words translated from Swedish of Gustaf Fröding by CWS (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - Untitled manuscript, holograph (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems, typescript (Box 15)
  - Byron the Modern, A Re-Appraisal, holograph essay (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - Streamlined Grandma, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Buying a Preset in Brittany, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Summary of 'Susie's Grandmother', typescript (Box 15)
  - Misc. writings (Box 15)
  - Misc. writings (Box 15)
  - Untitled fragment, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Tercentenary Ode, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Selma Lagerlof at Home, holograph essay (Box 15)
  - The Day of Judgment, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - The Grand Tour – Columbusing (Box 15)
  - Richard Wagner, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Georges Bizet, holograph poem (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - The Ash-Can School of Literature, holograph essay (Box 15)
  - Tchaikovsky, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Claude Debussy, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Adventures in the Art of Teaching, holograph essay (Box 15)
  - What, No Rhyme for it?, typescript and holograph poem (Box 15)
  - Misc. essays, holograph (Box 15)
  - The Cloud's Brother, holograph poem (Box 15)
  - The Two Dragons, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems, holograph (Box 15)
  - Selection from Moberg's Novel, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems, holograph (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems, holograph (Box 15)
  - England Reclaimed by Sir Osbert Sitwell, review by CWS typescript and holo. (Box 15)
  - Lead, Kindly Light by Vincent Sheean, review by CWS typescript and holo. (Box 15)
  - Untitled essay, typescript and holograph (Box 15)
  - Misc. poems (Box 15)
  - On the Trail of a Hero, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Illumination, typescript and holograph story (Box 15)
  - Misc. writings (Box 15)
  - Fragment of play, holograph (Box 15)
  - The Deathless Don, typescript play (Box 15)
  - AB, typescript play (Box 15)
  - Tristan the Hero, typescript play (Box 15)
  - The Countess Valenska, typescript play (Box 15)
  - Aunt Elsbettel, typescript play (Box 15)
  - Sunset Harbor, typescript novel (Box 15)
  - Calantha, typescript play (Box 15)
  - A. Edward Newton, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Illumination, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Basic Thinking, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - Love and Law, typescript play (Box 15)
  - Unidentified play, typescript (Box 15)
  - The End of Every Maid's Desire, typescript story (Box 15)
  - Edna St. Vincent Millay, as Poet and as Person, typescript essay (Box 15)
  - The Ineffable Name: A Fantasy of the World War, typescript story (Box 15)
  - The Port of Friendly Faces, typescript poem (Box 15)
  - Misc. writings (Box 15)
  - Misc. clippings in "Clipping File" (Box 16)
  - The Egoist, typescript play (1 loose, 1 bound) (Box 16)
  - A Daughter of Boston, typescript novel (Box 16)
  - Will's Reformation: A Dramatic Fantasy, typescript play (2 copies) (Box 16)
  - Dram o' Dream, typescript play (Box 16)
  - A Quaker Mother, typescript and manuscript play (Box 16)
  - The Flower Seller, typescript novel (Box 16)
  - Misc. notebooks (Box 16)
  - Harcum Junior College Yearbook, 1943 (Box 16)
  - Misc. poems on cities, typescript (Box 16)
  - Mustard Magill, manuscript novel (Box 16)
  - Misc. poems and 'Lyrics and Songs', typescript (Box 16)
  - Publications with poems by CWS
    - Presbyterian Life "The Animal's Paradise" p.24, 9/15/1963 (Box 17)
    - The Stratford Magazine "A Woman's Body" p.23-32, Feb 1926 (Box 17)
    - The Personalist "The Tide of Beauty" p.97-98 (removed), April 1925 (Box 17)
    - The Haverfordian "Sappho LII" p.128, Dec. 1901 (Box 17)
    - The Forum "The Meeting of Christ and Pan: An Easter Ballad" (reprint), April 1924 (Box 17)
    - The Bellman "Zuloaga" p.681, 6/21/19 (Box 17)
    - Germantowne Crier "From Wissahickon Park on a Drab – Afternoon in Early Summer' p.54 and "Golden Blizzard" by – Lisl Stork, May 1962 (Box 17)
    - Theater Arts Monthly "Actor to playwright" p. 818 (only – title page and poem), Nov 1929 (Box 17)
    - The Lyric "Re-Consecration" p.2, Nov 1924 (Box 17)
    - The Lyric "To a Turkey Buzzard" p.7, Feb 1925 (Box 17)
    - The American Soroptimist "Song in March" p.2, March 1994 (Box 17)
    - The Sonnet "The Source of Beauty" p.1, 1919 (Box 17)
    - Loose poems "To Joseph Sevem" and "Love and Life" (Box 17)
  - Publications with translations by CWS
    - The Wave "Communion" p.53, Christmas 1922 (Box 17)
    - Poetry "The Wooden Castle" p.145-149 (2 copies), June 1923 (Box 17)
    - The Orpheus Club "Sea Song" p.11, 12/10/30 (Box 17)
    - Poetry "Father, Where do Wild Swans Go?" p.73, Nov 1922 (Box 17)
    - The American Scandinavian Review "Via Media" p.674, Nov 1922 (Box 17)
    - The American Scandinavian Review "The Blunder – Sonata" p.552, Sept 1931 (Box 17)
    - The Choir Leader "We Worship Thee" p.10, Sept 1958 (Box 17)
  - Publications with Reference to CWS
    - Contemporary Verse, back cover, Aug 1916 (Box 17)
    - Play and Poetry Shop Talk p.15, 1916-1941 (Box 17)
    - American Weave p.65, June 1967 (Box 17)
    - The Franklin Inn Club p.24, 1956 (Box 17)
    - The Indian P.E.N. p.122, 8/1/1951 (Box 17)
    - The Horace Club (1877-1917) speech by Mr. Stork Jr. p.13-22 (Box 17)
  - Publications with Articles by CWS
    - "The Influence of the Popular Ballad an Wordsworth and Coleridge" (Box 17)
    - "The Poetry of Viktor Rydberg" (Box 17)
    - The Parish News "Philadelphianum in Art", Nov 1922 (Box 17)
    - Bonniers Månads Häften "Joseph Hergesheimer" p.16, Aug/Sept 1920 (Box 17)
    - The Nation "Frances Barton Gummere" p.109, 7/26/1919 (Box 17)
    - The Gleam "A Danish Lyric for Autumn" p.12 (2 copies, - 1 with article removed), Oct 1924 (Box 17)
    - Athenaeum Annals "Of Libraries" p.1-2, Oct 1956 (Box 17)
    - "Verner Von Heidenstam" (incomplete) (Box 17)
  - Poems Published in The Diplomat
    - "Whistler's Mother" p.16, May 1960 (Box 17)
    - "The Philosophic Cannibal" p.63, Feb 1961 (Box 17)
    - nothing published, Sept 1961 (Box 17)
    - "Exult and Repose!" p.45, July/Aug 1964 (Box 17)
  - Scandinavian Studies Magazine
    - "Verse translation from the Modern Scandinavian" by CWS – p.65 (2 copies), May 1948 (Box 17)
    - Aug 1952 (Box 17)
    - May 1958 (Box 17)
  - Adventures in the Art of Teaching, typescript (incomplete) (Box 17)
  - Wisconsin Poetry Magazine
    - (Mar/Apr Vol. V no. 4) "A Stone is a Person" and Cloud Intimations" by CWS p.12-13, 4 copies, 1 with poems removed (Box 17)
    - "The Mystic in the Grand Stand" p.4-5 (Issue 7.1), Sept/Oct 1958; 3 copies (Box 17)
    - "The Veil of Fog" p.31, Nov 1958; 2 copies, both with poem removed (Box 17)
    - June 1958 (Box 17)
    - Letter from Clara Catherine Prince: Founder and Editor (Box 17)
  - Visva-Bharati
    - Visva-Bharati Quarterly – Education number, 1947 (Box 17)
    - Visva-Bharati Quarterly "Gustaf Fröding: Sweden's Greatest Lyric Poet" p.290-295, Feb/April 1951 (Box 17)
    - Visva-Bharati Quarterly, Summer 1958 (Box 17)
    - Visva-Bharati Bulletin No. 9, July 1946 (Box 17)
    - Visva-Bharati Bulletin No. 10, Sept 1945 (Box 17)
    - "The Lyrical poems of Hugo Von Hoffmansthal", incomplete article by CWS; 2 copies (Box 17)
    - "Gustaf Fröding: Sweden's Greatest Lyric Poet", 2 copies
  - Incomplete story, typescript (p.5, 9-13) – American Scandian Review (Box 17)
  - SAAR (Box 17)
  - ARCHER Magazine
    - "The Life of Vision" p.51 – translation by CWS, 3/24/1927; 2 copies (Box 18)
    - (Numbers 3 and 4) "How Father God was Snowbound" p. 16; "Symbols of the Artist" p.38 – translations by CWS, 1929 (Box 18)
  - Sea and Bay – A poem: Chiefly Narrative (Box 18)
  - Visva-Bharati
    - Visva-Bharati Quarterly "The Lyrical poems of Hugo Von – Hoffmansthal" p225-232 by CWS (Box 18)
    - Visva-Bharati Bulletin No. 25, March 1946 (Box 18)
  - Legal Papers
    - Last Will and Testament of Charles Wharton Stork, 1940 (Box 18)
    - First Codicil to Will of Charles Wharton Stork (Box 18)
    - Deed to the Pennsylvania Co. for Insurance on Lives on Granting Annuities and Other Trustees to John Ennis (Box 18)
    - Agreement between CWS, Pennsylvania Co. and Vivian Orleans (Box 18)
    - Sur Account of the Pennsylvania Co. for Emma B. Stork (Box 18)
    - Title Papers (empty folder) (Box 18)
    - Last Will and Testament of Mary L. Wharton (Box 18)
    - Various Agreements and Adjudications (Box 18)
  - Poetry books by other authors
    - Herman Salinger (Box 18)
    - Howard Gordon Hanson (Box 18)
    - Florence Earle Coates (Box 18)
    - Martin S. Allwood (Box 18)
    - Leigh Hanes (Box 18)
    - Lillian Elizabeth Turner (Box 18)
    - Sanford L. Peele, Pat R. Willis and B. Tolson Willis (Box 18)
    - Katherine Wisner McCluskey (Box 18)
    - 1 Book 1 Leaf of Emma B. Stork (Box 18)
    - Various authors, 3 volumes (Box 18)
  - Published poems of CWS
    - Delaware Tercentenary 1638-1938 "Tercentenary Hymn" p.4 "The Quarter-Deck" (Box 18)
    - Two Christmas greetings from Christian Science Monitor (Box 18)
    - Boston Transcript "To George Meredith", 2/15/1928 (Box 18)
    - "Mont-Saint Michel" (Box 18)
    - "Ten Years of American Poetry" (Box 18)
    - The Saturday Evening Post "Sketches of an Athenian" p.33 and 98 (Box 18)
    - Old Penn Weekly Review "Eminent American Poet to Lecture" (Box 18)
  - Erica – A Modern Grand Opera (Box 18)
  - Sweden Speaks (Box 18)
  - Harcum Junior College Yearbook – Vibrations 1936 (Box 18)
  - Memberships Lists
    - Poetry Society of America (Box 18)
    - NY Center P.E.N. (Box 18)
  - Music scores (Box 18)
  - 5 Journals and/or notebooks (Box 18)
  - Misc. literature
    - Poetry (Box 19)
    - Clippings (Box 19)
    - Receipts (Box 19)
    - Drawings (Box 19)
    - Correspondence (Box 19)
  - Programs
    - "The Flower Seller" by CWS (Box 19)
    - Sculpture Exhibition (Box 19)
    - Society of Friends of Roerich Museum – CWS President Camegie Hall Program (Box 19)
    - "The House That Bert Built" (Box 19)
    - Dinner for Friends of CWS (Box 19)
    - Harcum Junior College Commencement Exercises, 1952 (Box 19)
    - "Peg o' My Heart" by CWS (Box 19)
    - "Drawbacks" by CWS (Box 19)
    - "Tercentenary Hymn" words by CWS (Box 19)
    - "Time Will Tell" (Box 19)
    - The Mermaid Club Annual Dinner, 1906 (Box 19)
    - "The Younger American Poets", lecture Given by CWS (Box 19)
    - The Compositions of Axel Raoul Wachtmeister (Box 19)
    - The Browning Society of Philadelphia – Manuscript Night (Box 19)
    - The Browning Society of Philadelphia – Author's Night (Box 19)
    - The Browning Society of Philadelphia – 25th Annual Dramatic Performance (Box 19)
  - 1 Bank Book and 3 small Notebooks (Box 19)
  - Published poems by CWS (Box 19)
  - 3 Newspapers about Nazi sub that halted American vessel, 1939 (Box 19)
  - Fiyers and newspaper clippings regarding CWS and his work (Box 19)
  - Published essays by CWS (Box 19)
  - Articles, stories, and poems written or translated by CWS (Box 19)
  - Postcards and greeting cards sent to or from CWS (Box 19)
  - Newspaper clippings written by or about CWS (Box 19)
  - Clippings of poetry by CWS and others (Box 19)
  - Clippings of early WWII (Box 19)
  - Clippings of early WWII (Box 19)
  - Published works of CWS before 1920 (Box 19)
  - Book of drawings (Box 19)
  - Clippings of many poems by others (Box 19)
  - Scrapbook of several published works by CWS (Box 20)
  - Writings by CWS
    - "Three Volumes of Recent Verse" (Box 20)
    - "From Olympus to Asphalt" (Box 20)
    - "Personality and Art" (Box 20)
  - A Florentine Fantasy, translated from Swedish by CWS (Box 20)
  - Grand Mothers' Name Day, translated from Swedish by CWS (Box 20)
  - Erik Axel Karlfeldt, Swedish Home-Poet, by CWS (Box 20)
  - Israel's Christmases, translated from Swedish by CWS (Box 20)
  - Letters and Reviews by CWS
    - An Answer to Mr. D.H. Lawrence, letter (Box 20)
    - Daylight Magic for Old and Young, review (Box 20)
    - Authentic Mood, review (Box 20)
    - Names and Merit, review (Box 20)
    - Bill Boram, review (Box 20)
    - Assorted Creams, review (Box 20)
    - An Anticipatory Vacation, review (Box 20)
    - First Volumes and Anthologies, review (Box 20)
    - Hot, Cold, Moist, Dry, review
    - The Song of Songs, review (Box 20)
    - Parodists and Half-Masters, review (Box 20)
    - An Answer to Mr. D.H. Lawrence, letter (Box 20)
  - The Lady in White, translated from Swedish by CWS
  - Letters and reviews by CWS
    - To Our Friends the Newspapers, letter (Box 20)
    - The Silent Do We, review (Box 20)
    - Recent Verse, review (Box 20)
    - Here are Ladies, review (Box 20)
    - Enameled Surfaces: A Review of 'Ship's Log' by Grace Hazard Conkling, review (Box 20)
    - Post Millay-ism: Review of 'Frontier'by Isabel Fiske Conant, review (Box 20)
    - The Eugenic Aesthete: Review of 'Impressions and Comments' by Havelock Ellis, review (Box 20)
    - Review of Three poems: 'The Mirthful Lyre,' The Light Guitar,' and 'The-Laughing Muse' by Arthur Guiterman, review (Box 20)
    - Conservatives, Volumes of Verse, review (Box 20)
    - The Swallow Book by Ernst Toller and Ashley Dukes, review (Box 20)
    - Volumes of verse reviewed by CWS including 'My Brother's Face,' 'Who Lightly Sips,' 'A Love Lyric,' and 'Platonic Rivals', review (Box 20)
    - America the Fifties, review (Box 20)
    - Volumes of Verse Reviewed by CWS 'Hot, Cold, Moist, and Dry,' 'Sign-Posts' and 'A Harp in the Winds', review (Box 20)
    - Celestial Ardors: Review of 'Jupiter's Moons' by Gertrude Carver, review (Box 20)
    - Poetic Volumes Reviewed by CWS, 'Helen and Others,' and 'Poems,' review (Box 20)
  - Poems by CWS
    - The Crown and the Rose (Box 20)
    - November Twilight (Box 20)
    - The Surface (Box 20)
    - Progression (Box 20)
    - A Truth Song (Box 20)
    - The Sleeping Cherub (Box 20)
    - The Recompense (Box 20)
    - To a Penitent (Box 20)
    - Dependence (Box 20)
    - Marc Amoris (Box 20)
  - Poems Reviews by CWS
    - Loves and Losses of Pierrot (Box 20)
    - The poems of Adelaide Manola (Box 20)
    - Harvest (Box 20)
  - Letter sent from Mirror Lake, Essex County New York (Box 20)
  - Music in Industry: A Dramatic Sketch (Box 20)
  - Several poems by Charles Winship (Box 20)
  - On Board Old Ironsides: An Epic by CWS (Box 20)
  - Glimpses of the Far East, collection of poems (Box 20)
  - Mustard Magill, A World Series Idyll, novel by CWS (Box 20)
  - A Dancer in a Gage, story by CWS (Box 20)
  - King Ardamenes, long poem (Box 20)
  - NAVPAC: An Epic of the U.S. Navy (Box 20)
  - Sea and Bay, poem (Box 20)